<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
<template id="report_warrantycertificate_document">
    <t t-call="web.external_layout">
        <t t-set="doc" t-value="doc.with_context(lang=doc.partner_id.lang)" />
       
        <div class="page">
            <div class="oe_structure"/>
			
			<h2 name="title" class="mb-4 text-center">Warrany Certificate</h2>
			
			<p name="body1">
				The warranty is valid for a period of <span t-field="line.warranty"/> month(s) from the date of receipt by the customer for equipment that does not 
				require installation or the date of installation for machines and equipment. 
				Installation means the commissioning operations performed by the specialized personnel of the supplier. 
				The warranty loses its validity if unauthorized intervention is found on the equipment. 
				Parts identified by defective material or workmanship will be replaced free of charge by the supplier during the warranty period. manufacturing. 
				It will also fix any mounting defects. Defective spare parts replaced with functional ones will be returned to the supplier.
			</p>
			<p name="body2">
				Spare parts are provided for normal operation of the machine and not for defects that may occur in the following cases:<br/>
				<ul>
					<li>the instructions and instructions for use in the car manual are not followed or the machine is given another utility</li>
					<li>incorrect connection to the power supply</li>
					<li>in case of unauthorized repairs or modifications</li>
				</ul>
			</p>
			<p name="body3">
				Maintenance and service:<br/>
				All interventions on the equipment must be performed by specialized personnel <span t-field="doc.company_id.name"/>. Requests for repair services are made on the basis of a 
				written order sent to <span t-field="doc.company_id.partner_id.email"/>. The staff of the supplier will establish together with the client how to solve the 
				situation. 
				Depending on the working frequency of the machine, it is recommended to perform an overhaul no later than 12 months after purchase. 
				For cars that work in 2 or 3 shifts, the revisions must be made every 6 months.
			</p>
			<p name="body4" class="nb16">
				This certificate has been issued for invoice: <span t-field="doc.name"/> / <span t-field="doc.invoice_date"/>
			</p>
			<p name="body5" class="nb16">
				This document is certified for the product <span t-field="line.product_id.display_name"/>, serial: <span t-field="line.serial_number_id"/>
			</p>
        </div>
    </t>
</template>


<template id="report_warrantycertificate">
    <t t-call="web.html_container">
        <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
            <t t-foreach="doc.invoice_line_ids" t-as="line">
            	<t t-if="line.serial_number_id and line.product_id and line.product_id.type != 'service'">
            		<t t-call="diginesis_warranty.report_warrantycertificate_document" t-lang="doc.partner_id.lang"/>
            	</t>
            </t>
        </t>
    </t>
</template>

</odoo>
